

DILA RIZVINA NATAISHA

| dilarnataisha@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/dilarizvinan | dila-rn.vercel.app

An Electrical Engineering graduate from Universitas Gadjah Mada who has a passion for Front- end Web Development. During her time in college, she engaged in various activities that allowed her to develop her communication, leadership, and problem-solving abilities. These experiences, combined with her knowledge, allow her to approach problems with both technical and creative solutions to bring a unique perspective and work collaboratively with others to achieve success.

Education Level

Synrgy Academy Sep 2022 - Feb 2023

Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development

- SYNRGY Academy is a collaboration program between BCA and Binar Academy in the form of online bootcamp scholarship.
- During the six months of intensive online bootcamp, with project-based learning method, I learned about basic full-stack web
 development concepts such as responsive web design, object-oriented programming in JavaScript, DOM manipulation, building
 RESTful APIs and HTTP servers, creating single-page web applications, and projects deployment.
- Developed a Boarding House Rental Platform called "Omah Kos" for the final project with 18 team members and was given the opportunity to lead as the Project Manager.
- Enhanced my skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React.js, Next.js, Node.js, Express.js, Sequelize, Railway, Vercel, CI/CD and Git.

Universitas Gadjah Mada - D.I. Yogyakarta

Aug 2018 - Oct 2022

Undergraduate in Electrical Engineering, 3.24/4.00

- Gained a foundation in fundamental concepts and principles.
- Developed a comprehensive understanding of the various techniques and strategies used in control engineering.

Work Experiences

LUVIA Hijab Apr 2022 - Jun 2022

Graphic Designer

- Successfully created stunning designs for the LUVIA and LUVKID brands, including graphics for social media promotion, catalogues, and merchandise, using my expertise in Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator.
- Participated in product photography, photo editing, and video editing for LUVIA's social media content, ensuring that the brand's visual identity remained consistent and captivating to its audience.

PT Pertamina (Persero) RU VI Balongan

Jan 2021 - Feb 2021

Maintenance Execution Intern

- Dedicated my research to studying catalyst level control in a regenerator for the Residue Catalytic Cracker Unit (RCC) throughout my month-long internship.
- Gained invaluable experience and insights about how the system works.

Departemen Teknik Elektro dan Teknologi Informasi FT UGM

Oct 2020 - Dec 2020

Laboratory Assistant of Digital and Microprocessor

- Assisted the students to do lab works and simulations, such as Combinatorial Logic circuit, Digital Aritmethic, Digital I/ O
 Microprocessor, and Analog I/O Microprocessor, all while honing ESP32 Microcontrollers and Autodesk Tinkercad skills.
- Developed abilities as an educator. Working with students on these critical concepts not only deepened my own understanding of these technologies, but also enabling me to communicate complex ideas with clarity and confidence.

Organisational Experience

KMTETI FT UGM Feb 2020 - Dec 2020

Vice Head of Information and Communication Division

- Assisted the Head of the Information and Communication Division in completing their duties, helping to complete a range of essential
 tasks, including designing the cabinet logo, editing and enhancing cabinet release photos, and fulfilling a wide range of graphic design
 needs for KMTETI FT UGM.
- Took part in crafting visually stunning covers for announcements and special day celebrations to developing compelling designs for press releases, Voltamagz magazine, Voltanews Bulletin, and Infographics, I was committed to delivering high-quality work that caught the eye and captivated the attention of our audience while also delivering valuable content.

KMTETI FT UGM Jan 2019 - Feb 2020

Treasurer of Information and Communication Division

- · Responsible for managing financial affairs, including financial planning, mapping and record-keeping, and financial reporting.
- Fulfilled the graphic design needs of KMTETI FT UGM, using my expertise in design to create visually stunning content that effectively conveyed important information to our audience.

Jun 2019 Jun 2019 - Oct 2019

Head of Multimedia Team

- Managed the multimedia team to ensure all design needs were met for the event. This included creating eye-catching posters, banners, and covers for reminders.
- · Actively participated in documenting the event to capture the spirit of the occasion.

PPSMB Kesatria FT UGM May 2019 - Aug 2019

Member of Design Division

- Created ornaments and edited co-cards for staffs of PPSMB Kesatria 2019.
- Created a design for an infographic called "Ngulik Teknik" to present pieces of information about the departments in FT UGM.

Find IT! UGM Oct 2018 - Apr 2019

Member of Multimedia Team

- Created icons to represent the competitions, poster for "Competitive Programming" competition, cover for announcements, cover for a proposal, and certificates.
- Took a part in documenting the event.

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Graphic Design: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Corel Draw, Adobe Lightroom
- Frontend Web Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Next.js, React.js
- · Backend Web Development: RESTful API, Express.js, PostgreSQL, Node.js, Railway
- Electrical Engineering Softwares: MatLAB, PSIM, LT Spice, Node- RED, InfluxDB, Grafana, PSIM.
- SBC and Microcontrollers: Raspberry Pi, Arduino, ESP32
- Other Programming language: Python, C++, C